question_data = [
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]